const questions = [
  {
    question: 'Questão 1',
    answers: [
      'Resposta 1',
      'Resposta 2',
      'Resposta 3',
      'Resposta 4',
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  },
  {
    question: 'Questão 2',
    answers: [
      'Resposta 5',
      'Resposta 6',
      'Resposta 7',
      'Resposta 8',
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: 'Questão 3',
    answers: [
      'Resposta 9',
      'Resposta 10',
      'Resposta 11',
      'Resposta 12',
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: 'Questão 4',
    answers: [
      'Resposta 13',
      'Resposta 14',
      'Resposta 15',
      'Resposta 16',
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: 'Questão 5',
    answers: [
      'Resposta 17',
      'Resposta 18',
      'Resposta 19',
      'Resposta 20',
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: 'Questão 6',
    answers: [
      'Resposta 21',
      'Resposta 22',
      'Resposta 23',
      'Resposta 24',
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: 'Questão 7',
    answers: [
      'Resposta 25',
      'Resposta 26',
      'Resposta 27',
      'Resposta 28',
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  },
  {
    question: 'Questão 8',
    answers: [
      'Resposta 29',
      'Resposta 30',
      'Resposta 31',
      'Resposta 32',
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: 'Questão 9',
    answers: [
      'Resposta 33',
      'Resposta 34',
      'Resposta 35',
      'Resposta 36',
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: 'Questão 10',
    answers: [
      'Resposta 37',
      'Resposta 38',
      'Resposta 39',
      'Resposta 40',
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
];

export default questions;